JUAN URIBE

FULL-STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I have a clear, logical mind with a practical approach to problem-solving and a drive to see things through to completion. I have more than three years of experience in electronic automation and almost two years in supervising teams and projects across this line of production. I am eager to learn, I enjoy overcoming challenges, and I have agenuine interest in building my bestversion.

PERSONAL SKILLS

Self-motivated Creative Adaptable Having an eye for detail Problem-solver

CONTACT

+57 300 881 0670 juanuribe513@gmail.com

REFERENCES

Isabel Restrepo Family +57 323 464 3257

Harlinson Chavarro Software developer +57 312 512 76 26

Jhon Correa Head of maintenance +57 313 662 9773

PROFILE

I am extremely motivated to constantly develop my skills and grow professionally. I am confident in my ability to come up with solutions to the challenges I may face.

EXPERIENCE

MAINNTENANCE & ELECTRONIC AUTOMATION Fahilos S.A | Oct 2014 - Dec 2016

Serve as a point of communication between Karl Mayer / Jakob Müller AG Frick and Fahilos.

Leading processes of technological updating of machinery.

Perform corrective and preventive maintenance.

MAINTENANCE SUPERVISOR

C.I PACK S.A.S | Feb 2017 - Dec 2018

Maintenance supervisor of a water treatment plant at 90% and 1000 BHP coal fired boiler.

Supervise the correct operation and carry out preventive maintenance of the air network and installed compressors.

Keep the gas emission control and water purity records up to date. $% \label{eq:control} % \label{eq:controlled} % \label{eq:controlled} % \label{eq:controlled} % \label{eq:con$

HEAD OF MAINTENANCE

Fahilos S.A | Dec 2018 - Jun 2020

Carry out maintenance schedules and shift schedules for maintenance staff. Take control of costs and budgets of the maintenance area.

Order machinery and spare parts by keeping an orderly database.

Perform preventive and corrective maintenance to dyeing machines, printing machines, winding machines and looms.

Make a rigorous safety control of machinery under the supervision of the ARL. Give inductions on boiler safety and training in safe electrical and electronic revision to maintenance staff.

Train in a correct way to the interns in the area of specialization that they have. Serve as a point of communication between Karl Mayer / Jakob Müller AG Frick and Fabilos.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR

I.T.M University (Electronic Automation) | 2012 - 2016 PROFESSIONAL

Cisco Networking Academy (Devops) | 2020 Holberton School (Software Engineering) | 2020 - 2021

TECHNOLOGIES

Technologies that I am continuously learning and I want to continue to learn more from them.

Data bases

MongoDB | MySQL

Back-end

Python3 | Node.js | Flask

Front-end

React